Angel's Playbox Entrance
Monster: Toy Box
Doppellusion
Shadow Stomp
Sylph Cutter
Status Effect
Stunned
Doppellusion
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 9
Dreamlord
Repair
Defense: 88
Defense: 200
2,117 EXP acquired
"The Upsetter" title acquired
Defeat a Dreamlord with a party of two
members or less at a level 70% or lower
than the recommended level
Attack and Speed increase by
15% when fighting higher-level enemies
Tin Sword
Attack: +9
Market Price: 2,400,000G
A Tin Knight's sword
Intermediate Wind Magic Skill Book
Market Price: 20,000,000G
Unlocks Intermediate Wind Magic skill tree, granting access to
slicing single-target attacks, thundering area of effect attacks,
and tailwinds to boost movement speed
m 0 0 l 225 0 225 65 0 65)
Skill Book: 20,000,000G
Total: 63,840,000G
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade: 17,000,000G x2
Tin Sword: 2,400,000G x2
Bear Shield: 200,000G x2
Embryo Magic Stone: 1,300,000G
Tin Knight Magic Stone: 600,000G x3
Golden Raana Magic Stone: 600,000G x2
Patchwork Bear Magic Stone: 170,000G x2